{"data":[{"question":"________ people have a perfect place from their childhood that brings back lovely feelings.","a":"Most of","b":"Most","c":"Most the","d":"Most many","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Most + Noun \n- Most of + Pronoun\/ definite noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"With his father's guidance, Mozart ________ playing the clavier at the age of three and composing at the age of five.","a":"begun","b":"began","c":"begin","d":"begins","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (at the age of five).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"________ officials expect increases on the funding for higher education.","a":"A little","b":"Much","c":"Many","d":"Little","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"The area has ________ the richest and most expensive farmland in the country.","a":"some","b":"some of","c":"both a and b are correct","d":"some for","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Most of\/some of\/ none of: + definite noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Since 1969 there have been ________ attempts to find a political solution to that country problem.","a":"the number of","b":"a number of","c":"a great deal of","d":"a large amount of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use amount to refer to a quantity. Use number to refer to people or things that can be counted.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"________ fruit is grown in this area.","a":"Many","b":"A lots","c":"A lot of","d":"Few","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little\/ A lot of: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"They had spent so ________ time on gaining the independence.","a":"much","b":"many","c":"a lot","d":"very","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little\/ A lot of: uncountable noun.\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Too ________ factors are involved in getting a good job.","a":"much","b":"many","c":"both a and b are correct","d":"little","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little\/ A lot of: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"________ our products are sold overseas.","a":"Many of","b":"Much of","c":"A great deal of","d":"Little of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Much \/ a little\/ A lot of\/ a great deal of: uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Few\/a few\/many: countable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"________ screws have come loose. I'll have to tighten them.","a":"A little","b":"Several","c":"Much","d":"A great deal of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Several + plural and countable noun.\u00a0\n- Little\/much\/ a great deal of + uncountable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"}]}